Guide to the School of Medicine, Yale University, Records of the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of Deans George Blumer, Milton C. Winternitz, Stanhope Bayne-Jones, Francis G. Blake, and Cyril N. H. Long, 1888-1960; Accession 1961-A-002
  - General Correspondence
    - Farnam, Henry W., 1929 (Box 88, Folder 1841)
    - Farn~, Thomas W., 1920~35 (Box 88, Folder 1842)
    - Farnham, Louise, 1931 (Box 88, Folder 1843)
    - Farr, Charles E., 1926-1935 (Box 88, Folder 1844)
    - Farr Clifford B., 1926-1927 (Box 88, Folder 1845)
    - Farwell, John V., 1928-1942 (Box 88, Folder 1846)
    - Felton, Lloyd D., 1933 (Box 88, Folder 1847)
    - Ferris, Harry B., 1931-1941 (Box 88, Folder 1848)
    - Filer, Harry L., 1959 (Box 88, Folder 1849)
    - Finley, Knox H., 1930 (Box 88, Folder 1850)
    - Fisher, Samuel H. (corporation), 1921-1922 (Box 89, Folder 1851)
    - Fisk, Albert Atterbury, 1946 (Box 89, Folder 1852)
    - Fisk, Merl E., 1934 (Box 89, Folder 1853)
    - Fitkip., Abram E., 1929-1930 (Box 89, Folder 1854)
    - Flexner, Abraham, 1920-1931 (Box 89, Folder 1855 - 1856)
    - Flexner, Si.mon, 1924-1941 (Box 89, Folder 1857)
    - Forro, Frederick, Jr., 1947 (Box 89, Folder 1858)
    - Fox, James C., Jr., 1925 (Box 89, Folder 1859)
    - Frame:,-.Boy., 1946 (Box 89, Folder 1860)
    - Francis, Thomas, 1925 (Box 89, Folder 1861)
    - Frankfurter, Felix, 1929-1930 (Box 89, Folder 1862)
    - Freedman, Lawrence R., 1948 (Box 89, Folder 1863)
    - Freeman, Norman E., 1928 (Box 89, Folder 1864)
    - Furman, Robert H., 1946 (Box 89, Folder 1865)
    - Friedman, Ulrich, 1934 (Box 89, Folder 1866)
    - Fuldner, Russell, 1938 (Box 89, Folder 1867)
    - Furniss, Edgar S., 1929-1942 (Box 89, Folder 1868)
    - G general, 1923-1940 (Box 89, Folder 1869)
    - G miscellaneous, 1942 (Box 89, Folder 1870)
    - Gallagher, Roswell, 1934 (Box 89, Folder 1871)
    - Gardner, Leroy U., 1929-1935 (Box 89, Folder 1872)
    - Gardner, W. U., 1940 (Box 89, Folder 1873)
    - Garvan, Francis PI, 1930-1937 (Box 89, Folder 1874)
    - Gasser, Herbert S., 1935 (Box 89, Folder 1875)
    - Geiger, Arthur J., 1937-1940 (Box 89, Folder 1876)
    - Gelfan., Samuel, 1950-1951 (Box 89, Folder 1877)
    - Geraghty, E.M., 1933 (Box 89, Folder 1878)
    - Gessell, Dr., 1926-1927 (Box 89, Folder 1879)
    - Gibbs, J. Willard, 1939 (Box 89, Folder 1880)
    - Gibson, Donald F., undated (Box 89, Folder 1881)
    - Gilbert', Alfred' Carlton, 1931 (Box 89, Folder 1882)
    - Gilbert, Edwin C., 1959 (Box 89, Folder 1883)
    - Gilbert, Robert L, 1942 (Box 89, Folder 1884)
    - Gilchrist, John, 1923 (Box 89, Folder 1885)
    - Gillespie, Russell W.H., 1935 (Box 89, Folder 1886)
    - Gillespie, Samuel C., Jr., 1925 (Box 89, Folder 1887)
    - Gilman, Alfred, 1935 (Box 89, Folder 1888)
    - Glueck, Bernard, 1927 (Box 89, Folder 1889)
    - Glueck, Sheldon, 1937 (Box 89, Folder 1890)
    - Goldschmidt, Ernest F., 1930 (Box 89, Folder 1891)
    - Goldstein, Paul Stanley, 1947-1948 (Box 89, Folder 1892)
    - Goldmann, Franz F., 1920-1947 (Box 89, Folder 1893)
    - Goldstein, Richard M., 1933 (Box 89, Folder 1894)
    - Goldwate!, S.S., 1921-1934 (Box 89, Folder 1895)
    - Goodhart, H. L., 1926 (Box 89, Folder 1896)
    - Goodman, Louis S., 1943 (Box 89, Folder 1897)
    - Goodpasture, E.W., 1923-1929 (Box 89, Folder 1898)
    - Goodrich, Annie, 1929 (Box 89, Folder 1899)
    - Graham, Evarts A., 1928 (Box 89, Folder 1900)
    - Graham, Thomas Norris Cutujian, 1926 (Box 89, Folder 1901)
    - Greene, Phillips F., 1927 (Box 89, Folder 1902)
    - Greer, Harriet P., 1935 (Box 89, Folder 1903)
    - Gregg, Alan, 1939-1944 (Box 89, Folder 1904)
    - Gregiore, Paul, 1928 (Box 89, Folder 1905)
    - Greulich, W.W., 1934 (Box 89, Folder 1906)
    - Griggs, Edward Luther, 1940 (Box 89, Folder 1907)
    - Grozin, Maurice, 1921 (Box 90, Folder 1908)
    - Grunbaum, A.A., 1929-1932 (Box 90, Folder 1909)
    - Gustafson, Walter E., 1946-1947 (Box 90, Folder 1910)
    - Guy, Ruth, 1924 (Box 90, Folder 1911)
    - H general, 1925-1947 (Box 90, Folder 1912 - 1913)
    - H miscellaneous, 1930-1952 (Box 90, Folder 1914 - 1915)
    - Haddad, Fred, 1946 (Box 90, Folder 1916)
    - Hadley, Arthur T., 1912 (Box 90, Folder 1917)
    - Haff, Alexander O., 1945 (Box 90, Folder 1918)
    - Haggard, H. W., 1938 (Box 90, Folder 1919)
    - Hale, Thomas, Jr., 1935 (Box 90, Folder 1920)
    - Halpert, Bela, 1935 (Box 90, Folder 1921)
    - Halpern, Lena, 1935 (Box 90, Folder 1922)
    - Hamlin, Hannibal, 1960 (Box 90, Folder 1923)
    - Hami1ton, Alice, 1928-1935 (Box 90, Folder 1924)
    - Hamilton, James A., 1937 (Box 90, Folder 1925)
    - Harkavy, Emanuel E., 1930 (Box 90, Folder 1926)
    - Harley, George W., 1919 (Box 90, Folder 1927)
    - Harper, Paul, 1934 (Box 90, Folder 1928)
    - Harrison, Paul W., 1929-1934 (Box 90, Folder 1929)
    - Harrison, Ross G., 1923-19381940 (Box 90, Folder 1930)
    - Hart, James C., 1934 (Box 90, Folder 1931)
    - lfartwel1, John A., 1925-1931 (Box 90, Folder 1932)
    - Harvey, S. C., 1930-1934 (Box 90, Folder 1933)
    - Hawley, George M.B. (material on Wonderf'ul Phenomena"), 1930-1934 (Box 90, Folder 1934)
    - Health, University Department of, 1941-1942 (Box 90, Folder 1935)
    - Healy, William, 1929-1931 (Box 90, Folder 1936)
    - Heinemann, Martin, 1925-1939 (Box 90, Folder 1937)
    - Heiser, Florien, 1934 (Box 90, Folder 1938)
    - Henderson, Yandell, 1910-1939 (Box 90, Folder 1939)
    - Henderson, Yandell - on Functional Organization, 1919 (Box 90, Folder 1940)
    - Hendrick, Ives, 1931-1932 (Box 90, Folder 1941)
    - Henstell, H.H. - Medical Student, 1932-1935 (Box 90, Folder 1942)
    - Hersey, Harold W., 1919-1924 (Box 90, Folder 1943)
    - Hersey, Thomas, 1930 (Box 90, Folder 1944)
    - Hess, Orvan W., 1937 (Box 90, Folder 1945)
    - Higgins, Harold W., 1930 (Box 91, Folder 1946)
    - Hildebrand., Yngve., 1934 (Box 91, Folder 1947)
    - Hill, Harold W., 1935 (Box 91, Folder 1948)
    - Hilliard, Carlos G., 1938 (Box 91, Folder 1949)
    - Hillman, M.M., 1946 (Box 91, Folder 1950)
    - Hillsman, J.A., 1929-1931 (Box 91, Folder 1951)
    - Hilton, Maurice H., 1930 (Box 91, Folder 1952)
    - Himwich, H.E., 1925-1936 (Box 91, Folder 1953)
    - Hinchey, Richard J., 1941 (Box 91, Folder 1954)
    - Hirshfield, John W., 1937 (Box 91, Folder 1955)
    - Hiscock, Ira V., 1939-1942 (Box 91, Folder 1956)
    - Hoberman, Henry D., 1946 (Box 91, Folder 1957)
    - Hoff, Ebbe Curtiss, 1936 (Box 91, Folder 1958)
    - Hoff, Hebbel E., 1939-1942 (Box 91, Folder 1959)
    - Holden, Benedict M., 1930-1933 (Box 91, Folder 1960)
    - Holland, Edward W., 1928 (Box 91, Folder 1961)
    - Holland, Homer, 1938 (Box 91, Folder 1962)
    - Holman, Leslie B., 1926-1927 (Box 91, Folder 1963)
    - Homans, John, 1935-1937 (Box 91, Folder 1964)
    - Homberger, Erik, 1936 (Box 91, Folder 1965)
    - Hooker, Richard, 1932 (Box 91, Folder 1966)
    - Horn, Max, 1921 (Box 91, Folder 1967)
    - Houghton, Henry S., 1932-1934 (Box 91, Folder 1968)
    - Howes, Edward L., 1931-1937 (Box 91, Folder 1969)
    - Howland, Charles P., 1932 (Box 91, Folder 1970)
    - Howland, John, 1924 (Box 91, Folder 1971)
    - Hubenet, Dr., 1947 (Box 91, Folder 1972)
    - Huiskamp, Dr. John E., 1927 (Box 91, Folder 1973)
    - Hull, Clark J.J., 1930-1934 (Box 91, Folder 1974)
    - Hull, Thomas G., 1906-1948 (Box 91, Folder 1975)
    - Hume, Edward H., 1928-1930 (Box 91, Folder 1976)
    - Humphreys, Storer P., 1941 (Box 91, Folder 1977)
    - Hunt, Alice M., 1930 (Box 91, Folder 1978)
    - Hunt, Willis R., 1939 (Box 91, Folder 1979)
    - Huntington, Julia, 1932 (Box 91, Folder 1980)
    - Huntington, Robert W., 1929-1930 (Box 91, Folder 1981)
    - Hurst, J.H., 1924 (Box 91, Folder 1982)
    - Hussey, Raymond, 1924-1935 (Box 91, Folder 1983)
    - I general, 1924 (Box 91, Folder 1984)
    - I, J, K miscellaneous, 1934-1942 (Box 91, Folder 1985)
    - I miscellaneous, 1942-1952 (Box 91, Folder 1986)
    - Igersheimer, Walter W., undated (Box 91, Folder 1987)
    - Interne Council of America, 1936-1939 (Box 91, Folder 1988)
    - Ipsen, J., 1948 (Box 91, Folder 1989)
    - Ives, Howard R., 1941 (Box 91, Folder 1990)
    - J general, 1920-1940 (Box 91, Folder 1991)
    - J miscellaneous., 1942-1952 (Box 91, Folder 1992)
    - Jacoby,. A.L., 1926-1927 (Box 91, Folder 1993)
    - Japanese Medical 1lission, 1923 (Box 91, Folder 1994)
    - Jeffery, M. P., 1921 (Box 91, Folder 1995)
    - Johnson, A. LeRoy, 1928-1937 (Box 92, Folder 1996 - 1997)
    - Johnson, Edgar M., 1917 (Box 92, Folder 1998)
    - Johnson,:F. B., 1932-1934 (Box 92, Folder 1999)
    - Johnson, Mordecai w., 1929 (Box 92, Folder 2000)
    - Jordan, Robert, 1927 (Box 92, Folder 2001)
    - Joslin, Elliott P., 1940 (Box 92, Folder 2002)
    - Joslin, Stuart L., 1944 (Box 92, Folder 2003)
    - Jurka, Edith, 1945-1952 (Box 92, Folder 2004)
    - K general, 1929-1940 (Box 92, Folder 2005)
    - K miscellaneous, 1942-1952 (Box 92, Folder 2006)
    - Ka1kstein, David, 1934 (Box 92, Folder 2007)
    - Kappers, A., 1928-1935 (Box 92, Folder 2008)
    - Kast, Ludwig, 1930-1932 (Box 92, Folder 2009)
    - Katzenstein, Rolf, 1938 (Box 92, Folder 2010)
    - Kaufman, C.E., 1937 (Box 92, Folder 2011)
    - Kaufman, Edwin C., 1933 (Box 92, Folder 2012)
    - Keating, Hubert F., 1937 (Box 92, Folder 2013)
    - Keller, A.G., 1915~32 (Box 92, Folder 2014)
    - Keller, Florence, 1944 (Box 92, Folder 2015)
    - Kelly, G. Lombard, 1934 (Box 92, Folder 2016)
    - Kennard, Margaret A., 1942-1943 (Box 92, Folder 2017)
    - Kennaway, E. L., 1929~34 (Box 92, Folder 2018)
    - Kennedy, Robert L.., 1936 (Box 92, Folder 2019)
    - Kerns, Harry N., 1930 (Box 92, Folder 2020)
    - Kilgour, F. G., 1948 (Box 92, Folder 2021)
    - Kimball, Arthur R.., 1930-1931 (Box 92, Folder 2022)
    - Kisch, Bruno, 1939-1940 (Box 92, Folder 2024)
    - Kleiner, Israel S.., 1924 (Box 92, Folder 2025)
    - Kleiner, S.B., 1935-1936 (Box 92, Folder 2026)
    - Kline, Benjamin S., 1930-1931 (Box 92, Folder 2027)
    - Klinghoffer, Kalmen A., 1946 (Box 92, Folder 2028)
    - Klumpp, T.G., 1937-1938 (Box 92, Folder 2029)
    - Kogl, Fritz, 1939 (Box 92, Folder 2030)
    - Krause, A.C., 1938 (Box 92, Folder 2031)
    - Kreshover, Seymour J., 1939 (Box 92, Folder 2032)
    - Kubie, Lawrence s., 1930 (Box 92, Folder 2033)
    - Kulp, Walter L., 1931 (Box 92, Folder 2034)
    - Kugelmass, I. Newton, 1922-1931 (Box 92, Folder 2035)
    - Kuh, Clifford, 1934-1942 (Box 92, Folder 2036)
    - L general, 1912-1948 (Box 92, Folder 2037)
    - L miscellaneous, 1930-1952 (Box 92, Folder 2038 - 2039)
    - LaField, William A., 1933 (Box 92, Folder 2040)
    - LaFleur, Maurice P., 1927-1928 (Box 92, Folder 2041)
    - Lambert, Alexander, 1929 (Box 92, Folder 2042)
    - Lambert, Robert, 1929 (Box 92, Folder 2043)
    - Lambert, Samuel W., 1939 (Box 92, Folder 2044)
    - Landis, Eugene, 1932 (Box 93, Folder 2045)
    - Laurens, Henry, 1921 (Box 93, Folder 2046)
    - Lawrason, F. Douglas, 1948 (Box 93, Folder 2047)
    - Lawson, George M., 1924 (Box 93, Folder 2048)
    - Lawson, George N., 1912 (Box 93, Folder 2049)
    - Leak, R.L., 1923 (Box 93, Folder 2050)
    - LeCompte, Philip M., 1934 (Box 93, Folder 2051)
    - Lee, Porter, 1926-1927 (Box 93, Folder 2052)
    - Lennox, Margaret, 1957 (Box 93, Folder 2053)
    - Leonard, John C., 1938-1945 (Box 93, Folder 2054)
    - Levy, David M., 1625 (Box 93, Folder 2055)
    - Lewis, Dwight M., 1921 (Box 93, Folder 2056)
    - Libman, Emanuel, 1930-1932 (Box 93, Folder 2057)
    - Lidz, Theodore, 1951 (Box 93, Folder 2058)
    - Liebow, A.A., 1935 (Box 93, Folder 2059)
    - Lillie, Frank R., 1931-1933 (Box 93, Folder 2060)
    - Linde, Joseph I., 1939 (Box 93, Folder 2061)
    - Lindsay, C. Purdy, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 2062)
    - Lindsay, Merrill Kirk, 1936-1937 (Box 93, Folder 2063)
    - Lindsey, Douglas, 1945-1946 (Box 93, Folder 2064)
    - Lippard, Vernon W., 1938 (Box 93, Folder 2065)
    - Livingston, Robert B., 1950 (Box 93, Folder 2066)
    - Lloyd, David P.C., 1943 (Box 93, Folder 2067)
    - Loeb, Jacques, 1923 (Box 93, Folder 2068)
    - Loe-we, Siegfried, 1935 (Box 93, Folder 2069)
    - Loewi, Otto, 1939 (Box 93, Folder 2070)
    - Lohman, Carl A., 1935-1938 (Box 93, Folder 2071)
    - Long, C.N.H., 1936-1947 (Box 93, Folder 2072)
    - Loth, Matilde [Folder contains photocopies of photographs of Matilde Loth, Yale M.D. 1922. Original photographs have been sent to YRG 48, Yale Photo Collection] (Box 93, Folder 2073)
    - Lowenstein, B.E., 1945 (Box 93, Folder 2074)
    - Lowrey, Lawson G., 1926-1927 (Box 93, Folder 2075)
    - Lozner', Eugene L., 1946 (Box 93, Folder 2076)
    - Luby, John F., undated (Box 93, Folder 2077)
    - Lusk, Graham, 1932 (Box 93, Folder 2078)
    - Lyman, D.R., 1956 (Box 93, Folder 2079)
    - M general, 1925-1946 (Box 93, Folder 2080 - 2081)
    - M miscellaneous, 1921-1952 (Box 93, Folder 2082 - 2084)
    - MacBrayer, Ralph.A., 1931-1932 (Box 94, Folder 2085)
    - McBride, Malcolm, 1929 (Box 94, Folder 2086)
    - MacCallum, W.G., 1930 (Box 94, Folder 2087)
    - McCulloch, W.B., 1934 (Box 94, Folder 2088)
    - McDonnell, Ralph Augustine, 1939 (Box 94, Folder 2089)
    - McEvitt, Joseph L., 1940 (Box 94, Folder 2090)
    - Macht, David Isaac, 1930-1933 (Box 94, Folder 2091)
    - McKeown, Raymond M., 1930 (Box 94, Folder 2092)
    - Mackes, C. B., 1928 (Box 94, Folder 2093)
    - McKinley, Earl B., 1934-1935 (Box 94, Folder 2094)
    - McLean, Senator G., 1922 (Box 94, Folder 2095)
    - McNulty, 1950 (Box 94, Folder 2096)
    - McQueeney, Andrew, 1925 (Box 94, Folder 2097)
    - Magnus-Levy, Adolf, 1940-1942 (Box 94, Folder 2098)
    - Maher, S.J., 1932-1935 (Box 94, Folder 2099)
    - Mailhouse, Max, 1937 (Box 94, Folder 2100)
    - Mandeville, Frederick B., 1928-1933 (Box 94, Folder 2101)
    - Markoff, Samuel T., 1937-1938 (Box 94, Folder 2102)
    - Marriott, T. McKim, 1931-1932 (Box 94, Folder 2103)
    - Marshall, Donald F., 1945 (Box 94, Folder 2104)
    - Martin', Kirby A., 1927 (Box 94, Folder 2105)
    - Matas, Rudolph, 1932 (Box 94, Folder 2106)
    - Mathias, Ernst, 1938 (Box 94, Folder 2107)
    - Maurer, Gordon B., 1932-1934 (Box 94, Folder 2108)
    - Maurer, Robert N., 1952 (Box 94, Folder 2109)
    - May, Mark A., 1930 (Box 94, Folder 2110)
    - Meader, R.G., 1942 (Box 94, Folder 2111)
    - Mendell, C.W., 1931 (Box 94, Folder 2112)
    - Mendillo, John C., 1936 (Box 94, Folder 2113)
    - Merrick, Theodore F., 1945 (Box 94, Folder 2114)
    - Mestre, Harold, 1934 (Box 94, Folder 2115)
    - Meye, Adolph, 1934 (Box 94, Folder 2116)
    - Mignone, Joseph, 1937 (Box 94, Folder 2117)
    - Miles, Walter and Catherine, 1931-1934 (Box 94, Folder 2118)
    - Miller, Earl R., 1938 (Box 94, Folder 2119)
    - Miller, Herbert c., 1945 (Box 94, Folder 2120)
    - Miller, Justin, 1931-1932 (Box 94, Folder 2121)
    - Miller, Ogden D., 1938 (Box 94, Folder 2122)
    - Miller, Orlando Jack, 1947-1948 (Box 94, Folder 2123)
    - Miller, William Snow, 1929 (Box 94, Folder 2124)
    - Millikan, Glenn Allan, 19.39 (Box 94, Folder 2125)
    - Millstein, Howard, 1929 (Box 94, Folder 2126)
    - Milne, John, 1946 (Box 94, Folder 2127)
    - Miscellaneous, 1950-1952 (Box 94, Folder 2128 - 2129)
    - Mislowitzer, Ernest, 1938 (Box 94, Folder 2130)
    - Mooney, Grace, undated (Box 94, Folder 2131)
    - Morey, Robert, 1940 (Box 94, Folder 2132)
    - Morris, Margaret Hoskins, 1924 (Box 94, Folder 2133)
    - Morse, Arthur, 1921 (Box 94, Folder 2134)
    - Mottet, N.K., 1949-'50 (Box 94, Folder 2135)
    - Moulton, Edward S., 1938 (Box 94, Folder 2136)
    - Munger, C.E., undated (Box 94, Folder 2137)
    - Murphy, Fred· T., 1929-1940 (Box 94, Folder 2138)
    - N. General, 1921-1949 (Box 94, Folder 2139)
    - N Miscellaneous, 1934-1952 (Box 95, Folder 2140 - 2141)
    - Nachmansohn, David, 1939 (Box 95, Folder 2142)
    - Nahum, Louis M., 1929-1934 (Box 95, Folder 2143)
    - National Coffee Roasters Association O.T. Osborn vs. M.I.T., 1924-1925 (Box 95, Folder 2144)
    - Nesbitt, Samuel, 1946 (Box 95, Folder 2145)
    - Neuhardt, Charles W., 1938 (Box 95, Folder 2146)
    - Nissen, Henry W., 1944-1958 (Box 95, Folder 2147)
    - de-No, Lorente, 1929 (Box 95, Folder 2148)
    - Nugent, Charles A., 1949 (Box 95, Folder 2149)
    - Nye, Robert N., 1920 (Box 95, Folder 2150)
    - O general, 1929-1943 (Box 95, Folder 2151)
    - O miscellaneous, 1931-1952 (Box 95, Folder 2152 - 2153)
    - Opie, Eugene L., 1931 (Box 95, Folder 2154)
    - Orr, John, 1931 (Box 95, Folder 2155)
    - Orton, Samuel T., 1928 (Box 95, Folder 2156)
    - Osborn, Minnott A., 1922-1923 (Box 95, Folder 2157)
    - Osborne, Oliver T., 1927-1926 (Box 95, Folder 2158)
    - Oughterson, Ashley W., 1930-1934 (Box 95, Folder 2159)
    - Owen, Arthur K., 1925 (Box 95, Folder 2160)
    - P general, 1922-1952 (Box 95, Folder 2161)
    - P miscellaneous, 1931-1952 (Box 95, Folder 2162 - 2163)
    - Pack, George T., 1940 (Box 95, Folder 2164)
    - Painter, Charles F., 1918 (Box 95, Folder 2165)
    - Pakchanian, A., 1935 (Box 95, Folder 2166)
    - Palmer, Walter W., 1920-1932 (Box 95, Folder 2167)
    - Pan American Sanitary Bureau, 1940-1943 (Box 95, Folder 2168 - 2169)
    - Parent's Magazine., 1940 (Box 95, Folder 2170)
    - Park, William H., 1931 (Box 96, Folder 2171)
    - Parmelee, Berkeley M., 1932 (Box 96, Folder 2172)
    - Parsons, Francis, 1928 (Box 96, Folder 2173)
    - Partree, H.T., 1937 (Box 96, Folder 2174)
    - Patino, J.F., 1949 (Box 96, Folder 2175)
    - Paton, Stewart, 1926 (Box 96, Folder 2176)
    - Patten, Bradley M., 1953 (Box 96, Folder 2177)
    - Paynter, Richard H., 1926-1927 (Box 96, Folder 2178)
    - Peabody, Francis W., 1920 (Box 96, Folder 2179)
    - Pearah,Norman B., 1924 (Box 96, Folder 2180)
    - Penfield, Wilder, 1929 (Box 96, Folder 2181)
    - Penner, Sidney L., 1938 (Box 96, Folder 2182)
    - Pepper, Dickinson S., 1934 (Box 96, Folder 2183)
    - Perham., H. S., 1937 (Box 96, Folder 2184)
    - Perkins, James L., 1933 (Box 96, Folder 2185)
    - Perina, Anson, 1946 (Box 96, Folder 2186)
    - Perry, Isabel H., 1928-1931 (Box 96, Folder 2187)
    - Peters, J.P., 1934 (Box 96, Folder 2188)
    - Petruccella, M.C., 1923 (Box 96, Folder 2189)
    - Petrunkevitch, Alexander, 1917-19 (Box 96, Folder 2190)
    - Petrus, Edward H., 1927-1928 (Box 96, Folder 2191)
    - Pfeiffer,.C.A., 1946 (Box 96, Folder 2192)
    - Phillips, Frank E., 1936-1937 (Box 96, Folder 2193)
    - Pierson, Emily Miller, 1924 (Box 96, Folder 2194)
    - PIng, Er-Chang, 1928 (Box 96, Folder 2195)
    - Pitman, Edwin P., 1914 (Box 96, Folder 2196)
    - Pitts, Herman Canfield, 1914,1960 (Box 96, Folder 2197)
    - Platt, Philip, 1930 (Box 96, Folder 2198)
    - Polk, Frank, 1929 (Box 96, Folder 2199)
    - Pond, Ashley, 1931-1937 (Box 96, Folder 2200)
    - Porter, I.N., 1946 (Box 96, Folder 2201)
    - Potsaid, M.S., 1952 (Box 96, Folder 2202)
    - Potter, Howard W., 1926-1927 (Box 96, Folder 2203)
    - Pratt, Joseph H., 1932-1933 (Box 96, Folder 2204)
    - Preston, Frederick A., 1929 (Box 96, Folder 2205)
    - Pruden, T. Mitchell, 1924 (Box 96, Folder 2206)
    - Q general, 1927-1937 (Box 96, Folder 2207)
    - R general, 1922-1944 (Box 96, Folder 2208)
    - R miscellaneous, 1930-1952 (Box 96, Folder 2209 - 2210)
    - Racca,Vittorio, 1934 (Box 96, Folder 2211)
    - Ramsy, Elizabeth M., 1929 (Box 96, Folder 2212)
    - Rand, Richard, 1935 (Box 96, Folder 2213)
    - Rand, William Henry, 1925 (Box 96, Folder 2214)
    - Rathburn, Walter L., 1916-17 (Box 96, Folder 2215)
    - Rennie, T.A.C., 1947 (Box 96, Folder 2216)
    - Rey, Dr., 1938 (Box 96, Folder 2217)
    - Rheinberger, Margaret, 1934 (Box 96, Folder 2218)
    - Richards, A.N., 1939 (Box 96, Folder 2219)
    - Riridge, Milo P., 1923 (Box 96, Folder 2220)
    - Ripley, Alfred L., 1928 (Box 96, Folder 2221)
    - Robbins, Clarence L., 1929 (Box 96, Folder 2222)
    - Roberge, George E., 1941 (Box 96, Folder 2223)
    - Roberts, F.W., 1929 (Box 96, Folder 2224)
    - Robinson, G. Canbey, 1922-1929 (Box 96, Folder 2225)
    - Robinson, Elliott S., 1933 (Box 96, Folder 2226)
    - Rodman, Charles Shepard, 1940 (Box 96, Folder 2227)
    - Rogers, Arthur (formerly Rotter), 1927 (Box 96, Folder 2228)
    - Rogers, James Ganilile, 1922-1932 (Box 96, Folder 2229)
    - Rogers, Platt H., 1937-1938 (Box 96, Folder 2230)
    - Root, Edward King, 1937 (Box 96, Folder 2231)
    - Rosen, Bernard J., undated (Box 96, Folder 2232)
    - Rosenthal, Gerhard, 1935 (Box 96, Folder 2233)
    - Roth, W.F., 1930-1931 (Box 96, Folder 2234)
    - Rous, Peyton, 1922-1928 (Box 96, Folder 2235)
    - Rowland, Lewi s P., 1948 (Box 96, Folder 2236)
    - Ruch, Theodore C., 1939 (Box 96, Folder 2237)
    - Ruggles, Arthur Hiler, 1925-1927 (Box 96, Folder 2238)
    - Rumberg, G.H., undated (Box 96, Folder 2239)
    - Russell, Donald Gardner, 1919 (Box 96, Folder 2240)
    - Russell, Thomas H., undated (Box 96, Folder 2241)
    - S general, 1924-1944 (Box 97, Folder 2242 - 2243)
    - S miscellaneous, 1923-1952 (Box 97, Folder 2244 - 2246)
    - Salmon, Thomas W., 1937-1938 (Box 97, Folder 2247)
    - Salomon, Kurt, 1937-1938 (Box 97, Folder 2248)
    - Sanford, Leonard J., 1888 (Box 97, Folder 2249)
    - Sapir, Edward, 1933:-1935 (Box 97, Folder 2250 - 2251)
    - Sapirstein, Milton, 1939 (Box 97, Folder 2252)
    - Saxholm, 1950-1951 (Box 97, Folder 2253)
    - Schick, Bela, 1934 (Box 97, Folder 2254)
    - Schoofs, F., 1927 (Box 97, Folder 2255)
    - Scoltren, Adrian, 1935-1943 (Box 97, Folder 2256)
    - Scoville, Helen M., 1933 (Box 97, Folder 2257)
    - Seymour, Charles, 1928-1939 (Box 97, Folder 2259)
    - Sharp, Ezra A., 1929 (Box 97, Folder 2260)
    - Shaw, Edward, 1936 (Box 97, Folder 2261)
    - Shelling, D.H., 1939 (Box 97, Folder 2262)
    - Shepherd, G.R., 1906 (Box 97, Folder 2263)
    - Sherrill, Henry Knox, 1939 (Box 97, Folder 2264)
    - Shove, Herman W., undated (Box 97, Folder 2265)
    - Sigerist, Henry E., 1933-1935 (Box 97, Folder 2266)
    - Silliman, Benjamin, undated (Box 97, Folder 2267)
    - Skinner, C.E., 1942 (Box 97, Folder 2268)
    - Sleath, Jack C., 1934 (Box 97, Folder 2269)
    - Smallman, Thomas F., 1929 (Box 97, Folder 2270)
    - Smith, Elliott Dunlap, 1931 (Box 97, Folder 2271)
    - Smith, Norman N., 1934 (Box 97, Folder 2272)
    - Smith, William Warren, 1929 (Box 97, Folder 2273)
    - Smith, Woodruff, 1932 (Box 97, Folder 2274)
    - Sokol, Joseph E., 1942 (Box 97, Folder 2275)
    - Solomon, H.C., 1926-1927 (Box 97, Folder 2276)
    - Spencer, Harvey, 1921 (Box 97, Folder 2277)
    - Sperry, F.N., 1941 (Box 97, Folder 2278)
    - Spielmeyer, W., 1929-1935 (Box 97, Folder 2279)
    - Springer, Arthur L., 1934 (Box 97, Folder 2280)
    - Sprunt, Douglas H., 1932 (Box 97, Folder 2281)
    - Stearn, Kurt, 1936-1938 (Box 97, Folder 2282)
    - Stearns, H.R., 1898 (Box 97, Folder 2283)
    - Steiner, Walter B., 1932-1938 (Box 97, Folder 2284)
    - Stetson, Paul R., 1937 (Box 97, Folder 2285)
    - Stevens, Marvin A., 1934-1937 (Box 97, Folder 2286)
    - Stewart, H.E., 1923-1926 (Box 97, Folder 2287)
    - Stillman, Charles, 1928 (Box 97, Folder 2288)
    - Stone, E.L., 1924 (Box 97, Folder 2289)
    - Strauss, John Steinert, 1947-1948 (Box 97, Folder 2290)
    - Strecker, Edward A., 1926-1927 (Box 97, Folder 2291)
    - Streit, George, 1938 (Box 97, Folder 2292)
    - Sullivan, Stanley L., 1921 (Box 97, Folder 2293)
    - Sutphin, Stuart B., 1929 (Box 97, Folder 2294)
    - Svedberg, T., 1937-1938 (Box 97, Folder 2295)
    - Swain, Henry L., 1940 (Box 97, Folder 2296)
    - Swift, Homer, 1928 (Box 97, Folder 2297)
    - Szent-Gyorgyi A., 1937 (Box 97, Folder 2298)
    - T general, 1921-1954 (Box 98, Folder 2299 - 2300)
    - T miscellaneous, 1930-1942 (Box 98, Folder 2301 - 2302)